{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Automatic Blind \u0026 Drape Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40469/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40469,"taskName":"Electronic Drape, Shade or Blind Opener - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Service Automatic Drape, Shade or Blind Opener","xmTaskDescriptor":"Automatic Blind \u0026 Drape Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1718,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Electric Window Drape Electronic Blinds","textMessagingName":"Repr Elec Window","rolloverLongDesc":"Devices can be controlled by timers, button, remote control or computers.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes mechanical \u0026 electronic parts.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Service Automatic Drape, Shade or Blind Opener.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Automatic Blind \u0026 Drape Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Electric \u0026 Motorized Blinds","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":24,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Electronic Drapes, Shades or Blinds Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Electronic Drape, Shade or Blind Opener - Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Electronic Drapes or Shade Project","urlName":"Electronic-Drape-Shade-or-Blind-Opener-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Automatic Blind \u0026 Drape Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Electric,Window,Drape,Electronic,Blinds,Motorized,Shade,vertical,drapes,draperies,custom,Opener,electrician","emcCategoryOid":-12079,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":757,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40469/":{"taskOID":40469,"originalTaskOID":40469,"setID":757,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5229,"questionDisplayText":"What Needs Repairing/Servicing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Check all repairs/servicing details you need","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2619,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Frame pulling out","answerDisplayText":"Frame pulling out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1819,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Damaged slat(s)","answerDisplayText":"Damaged slat(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1810,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Damaged cord(s)","answerDisplayText":"Damaged cord(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Split pleat","answerDisplayText":"Split pleat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5144,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remote control doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Remote control doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3732,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Manual button doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Manual button doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":692,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Additional remote control unit needed","answerDisplayText":"Additional remote control unit needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2162,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Electric eye needed on wall","answerDisplayText":"Electric eye needed on wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5229,"questionDisplayText":"What Needs Repairing/Servicing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Check all repairs/servicing details you need","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2619,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Frame pulling out","answerDisplayText":"Frame pulling out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1819,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Damaged slat(s)","answerDisplayText":"Damaged slat(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1810,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Damaged cord(s)","answerDisplayText":"Damaged cord(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Split pleat","answerDisplayText":"Split pleat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5144,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remote control doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Remote control doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3732,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Manual button doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Manual button doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":692,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Additional remote control unit needed","answerDisplayText":"Additional remote control unit needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2162,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Electric eye needed on wall","answerDisplayText":"Electric eye needed on wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2619,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Frame pulling out","answerDisplayText":"Frame pulling out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1819,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Damaged slat(s)","answerDisplayText":"Damaged slat(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1810,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Damaged cord(s)","answerDisplayText":"Damaged cord(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Split pleat","answerDisplayText":"Split pleat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5144,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remote control doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Remote control doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3732,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Manual button doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Manual button doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":692,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Additional remote control unit needed","answerDisplayText":"Additional remote control unit needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2162,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Electric eye needed on wall","answerDisplayText":"Electric eye needed on wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}